const questions = [
    {
        question: "Aren't you a web developer? Is this a real store?",
        answer: "Yes, this is a real store. As a part of my portfolio, I have built several template websites that utilize a multitude of skills and techniques. This thrift shop is one of my projects."
    },
    {
        question: "What are the shipping options?",
        answer: "Most items are likely to ship UPS."
    },
    {
        question: "Why are the clothes so wrinkled? That's not very professional.",
        answer: "These clothes have been sitting in boxes for years. This website is more of a testament of ability than an actual store I intend to make money with."
    },
    {
        question: "Are these clothes clean?",
        answer: "I'll wash them before shipping."
    },
    {
        question: "Will an item restock?",
        answer: "No. All items are personal things I have purchased over the years that are gathering dust at this moment. I have no intentions to restock any particular items."
    },
    {
        question: "Is my card information secure?",
        answer: "Yes. I use Stripe to manage the checkout process. I never see, nor have access to, your personal card information."
    },
    {
        question: "I am local. Can we meet in person?",
        answer: "Possibly. Due to security concerns, I will probably not meet anyone in person, but I will consider it if the need arises."
    },
    {
        question: "How can I request additional sizes?",
        answer: "You can't. What you see is what I have."
    },
    {
        question: "What is your return policy?",
        answer: "No returns are accepted."
    },
    {
        question: "What about cancellations?",
        answer: "If I determine it is in our best interest to cancel, I will cancel an order and refund any money collected."
    },
    {
        question: "How long is shipping?",
        answer: "As long as it takes. UPS is usually only a few days."
    },
    {
        question: "Can you list my items?",
        answer: "No. I can, however, build you a website and allow you to sell your own.  I am not in the business of reselling. Check out my main website, where you can contact me to build you a custom website of your own!"
    },
    {
        question: "Are prices negotiable?",
        answer: "No."
    },
    {
        question: "I have a suggestion. How can I get in touch with you?",
        answer: "Use my Contact Me page. I cannot promise you I'll implement your suggestion, but I welcome your opinion."
    },
    {
        question: "Do you offer bundle discounts?",
        answer: "Not at this time. Due to the amount of coding required to add those conditions, I've opted to charge less per item than originally planned to compensate not having bundle discounts."
    }
]

export default questions;